Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Photographs
    - Penobscot Bay, ME, aboard Turtle, Lynda, Steve, Ben, Mary Morgan, 1996 Jun 30; negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben picture in frame, baby seal, Moose Pt. Park, cedar waxwings, 1996 Jul 8; negatives (Box 528)
    - Camden, ME, yard sale, age 93 before move to CA, Ben signing baby, 1996 Aug; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben and Steve Parker, Pocket Books photo shoot, Boston Common, 1996 Sep 19; prints, negatives; 2 folders (Box 528)
    - Ben rowing, Curtis Island, lunar eclipse, 1996 Sep 27; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben rowing, Curtis Island lighthouse, Camden harbor, Nancy Symington's house, 1996 Oct 6; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben on porch, purple scarf, interview, Camden, ME, 1996 Oct 8; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben at cove, La Jolla, CA, 1997; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - Mexican dance, Ben, 1997; negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben's last days, Sue Ferrel's ceremony, Sunday morning market, Barbara, Joan, Annie, Linda, 1997 Jul; prints, negatives (Box 528)
    - La Jolla Cove, FA, Jane lifeguard board, wild animal park, 1997 Jul 25-29; negatives (Box 528)
    - Ben and Mary Morgan Christmas card, 1997 Dec; prints (Box 528)
    - Ben's last days, La Jolla, CA, 1997-1998; prints, negatives; 4 folders (Box 529)
    - Ben's last days, La Jolla, CA, yoga center, Noel Fell, 1997-1998; prints, negatives; 2 folders (Box 529)
    - San Diego Psychological Association Award, Bryce going away party, 1998 Feb 20-21; prints, negatives (Box 529)
    - Ben and Mary Morgan, day before death, 1998 Mar 15; slides (Box 529)
    - La Jolla, CA, children's beach, seals, Karen's flowers, 1998 Apr 2; negatives (Box 529)
    - Machias Seal Island, New Brunswick, 1998 Jun 23; negatives (Box 529)
    - Ben's memorial service, reception, children, 1998 Aug 29; prints, negatives (Box 529)
    - Mary surfing; includes correspondence, 1999; prints (Box 529)
    - Disney, Orlando, FL., Discovery Island, 1999 Feb; negatives (Box 529)
    - Disney, Orlando, FL., Jake, bare butt, 1999 Feb; negatives (Box 529)
    - Disney, Orlando, FL., wilderness park, animal kingdom, Harriet, Paul, 1999 Feb; negatives (Box 529)
    - Tortola, BVI, Vivi, Piers, Paloma, 1999 Feb; negatives (Box 529)
    - Havana, Cuba, Mary Morgan, Patrick, 1999 Mar; negatives; 3 folders (Box 529)
    - Market, Patrick, Museum of Music, 1999 Mar; negatives (Box 530)
    - Parrot eating flowers, lily pond, 1999 Mar; negatives (Box 530)
    - Mark in Maine, 1999 Mar 26; negatives (Box 530)
    - Lincolnville beach, ME, Andy, Mark, 1999 Apr; negatives (Box 530)
    - Wayfarer, travel lift, 1999 Apr 24 - 25; negatives (Box 530)
    - New York City, NY, Ben's birthday party, 1999 May 2; prints, negatives (Box 530)
    - Mary Morgan, Ireland Trip, 1999 May-Jun; prints, negatives; 4 folders (Box 530)
    - Santa Cruz, CA, Darling house, 2000; negatives (Box 530)
    - Seals, surfing, sunset, Mary Morgan, others, 2000 Feb; prints, negatives (Box 530)
    - Santa Cruz, CA, Mary Morgan surfing, 2000 Jul; prints, negatives (Box 530)
    - Audubon Society, birding trip, Steve Kress, 2000 Sep; negatives (Box 531)
    - Central Park, NY, Doug, Lee, Jake and Judy, Hilton Head, 2000 Sep; negatives (Box 531)
    - Cuba, Tito Shizuho, gardener, 2001; negatives (Box 531)
    - Yosemite, CA, 2001 Oct; negatives (Box 531)
    - Galapagos, 2001 Nov; negatives (Box 531)
    - Family reunion, 2001 Dec; negatives (Box 531)
    - Miscellaneous nature, 2002; negatives (Box 531)
    - Cuba, 2002 Feb-Mar; negatives (Box 531)
    - Joplin, MO, Javier Gonzalez Quintana, 2002 Apr; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - New York, Orlando's graduation, 2002 May; negatives (Box 531)
    - Vancouver, 2002 Jun; negatives (Box 531)
    - Maine, 2002 Aug; negatives (Box 531)
    - Boston, MA, Javier Gonzalez Quintana, 2002 Aug-Sep; negatives (Box 531)
    - Santa Cruz, CA, wedding, 2002 Sep 2; negatives (Box 531)
    - Javi [Javier Gonzalez Quintana] and Mary Morgan, 2002 Sep 13; negatives (Box 531)
    - San Francisco Giants, Javier Gonzalez Quintana, 2002 Oct; negatives (Box 531)
    - World Series, Halloween, 2002 Oct; negatives (Box 531)
    - San Francisco Symphony, Alishia de Larrosha, 2002 Nov 6; negatives (Box 531)
    - Art21 Gallery, Patrick treats Javi, performance, 2002 Nov 15; negatives (Box 531)
    - Carmel, CA, 2002 Nov 16-17; negatives (Box 531)
    - Mt. Shasta, 2002 Nov 27-29; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - Christmas, Sacramento, CA, Howard home, 2002 Dec; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - Skywalker Ranch, Santa Rosa, CA, 2003 Jan 15-16; negatives (Box 531)
    - Ritz hotel, elephant seals, Half Moon Bay, 2003 Feb 28-29; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - Javi's birthday party, 2003 Mar 1; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - White House, Howard and Gail, 2003 Mar 16; negatives (Box 531)
    - Daffodils, zoo, Frog, Judy, Ruth, 2003 Mar 21-29; contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - Yosemite, CA, waterfall, Half Dome, 2004; contact sheet, negatives; black-and-white (Box 531)
    - [Album pages, unidentified], undated; appear to be from several different albums; includes Virgin Islands, Tortola, other locations (Oversize 13)
    - Allen and Holly Levin, signed and inscribed to Spock on reverse, from Allen and Holly, undated; prints (Oversize 10)
    - Andy Spock, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - Año Nuevo, CA elephant seals, undated (Box 531)
    - Ben with babies, undated; prints, contact sheet, negatives (Box 531)
    - Ben on boat, blue jacket, undated; prints, negatives (Box 531)
    - Ben fishing, undated; negatives (Box 531)
    - Ben and Jane, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - Ben, Jane, infant (either Michael or John), undated; prints, negatives (Box 531)
    - Ben, Jane, Mike, John, early family photos, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - Ben, Jane, Mike, Judy, Don, Peter, Susannah, undated; prints; includes one of Ben playing ping-pong (Box 531)
    - Ben, Ladies Home Journal portraits, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - "To Ben Love Mary Our Vacation" [album pages; probably Virgin Islands], undated; prints (Oversize 11)
    - Ben and Mary Morgan, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - Ben and Mary Morgan on boat, undated; prints (Box 531)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan and others, undated; prints; 2 folders (Box 532)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan and others, undated; negatives; 13 folders (Box 532)
    - Ben, Mary Morgan, signing book, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Ben, medical panel, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Ben, publicity photos, undated; prints, negatives; includes Ben alone, with others, with students, with mothers and children; 2 folders (Box 532)
    - Ben, speaking at Tuskegee Institute in Alabama, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Ben, miscellaneous, undated; prints; some alone, some with others (Box 532)
    - Ben, miscellaneous, undated; prints; some alone, some with others; includes several of Ben interacting with children (Oversize 10)
    - Berkeley, Piedmont House, undated; prints, negatives; Ben, Mary Morgan, others (Box 532)
    - Brine Bennett's, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Bust of Ben, undated; prints; artist not identified (Box 532)
    - Camden, ME, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Carapace, miscellaneous, undated; prints, negatives (Box 532)
    - Carolyn Zachary, Nancy Zachary, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Colyn Lee Cameron, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Dodie, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Elizabeth [illegible] wedding, undated; negatives (Box 532)
    - Ginger Councille, miscellaneous, undated; negatives, slides (Box 532)
    - "Good Citizen Dr. Spock" photoessay, U.S. Information Agency, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Jane Spock portraits, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Joe Dyer, Ben's roommate at Yale, undated; prints; pictured with unidentified woman (Box 532)
    - John Spock; wedding, others, undated; prints (Box 532)
    - Kathryn O'Neal; Dennis and John; Hannah, Mark and Sally, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - Kim Loveless and Ginger, Virgin Islands, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - Kim Rose wedding; Ben and MM at Kay's, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Linus Pauling and wife Ava Helen, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Mary Morgan and Javier Gonzalez Quintano, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - Mary Morgan signing document, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - Mike and John Spock, portraits as children, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Mike and Judy, Dece first day of school, Curtis Cove, ME, undated; contact sheet, negatives (Box 533)
    - Molly Spock, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Nanny Betty birthday party, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - New Haven, CT, places Ben used to live, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Norma Nero, Cleveland OH, Spock's secretary, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - North Vietnam, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Passport photos, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Protests, miscellaneous, undated; prints, negatives (Box 533)
    - Russel Wills, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - SANE event, Hotel Commodore, Steve Allen, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Shirly, John Spock, Mary, Magidson's party, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Spock women's group, undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - SYDA foundation; Faye, Roger, [illegible], undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Turtle, undated; prints, negatives (Box 533)
    - Wedding negatives [possibly Ginger's?], undated; negatives (Box 533)
    - WQED photographs, Ben and Jane, Florence Marcus, others, undated; prints (Box 533)
    - Unidentified contact sheets with negatives, undated; 2 folders (Box 533)
    - Unidentified group photo, undated; several young adults in Western garb, printed on tin (Box 533)
    - Unidentified negatives, undated (Box 533)
    - Unidentified prints, undated; includes matchbook with Ben and Mary on cover (Box 533)
    - Unidentified slides, undated (Box 533)
    - Mary Morgan's notes about photographs, undated; about ten pages of notes with "file number", dates and titles; file numbers don't seem to correspond to any information on photo sleeves or folders (Box 533)
  - Pins and necklaces, includes Benjamin Spock nametag, "BS" monogram, doves, necklace with "War is not healthy for children and other living things" quote (Box 534)
  - Posters, etc., posters, fliers, other publicity for speeches, lectures, personal appearances, etc. by Spock
    - An Alternative to the Property Parties: Spock/Hobson, People's Party and Peace and Freedom Party, [1971] (Oversize 3)
    - "Ask Dr. Spock About…" cover mockups (Oversize 3)
    - Baby and Child Care, Revised/Expanded Edition, mounted bookstore poster for revised/expanded edition, with Steven J. Parker (Map-case 60)
    - Dissent and Social Change: Dr. Benjamin Spock, sponsored by Ottawa Committee for Peace and Liberation (Oversize 3)
    - Dr. Benjamin Spock / The Dangers of Nuclear Power to Children, 1978; signed and inscribed to Spock from Carter Wentworth, front and back (Oversize 3)
    - Dr. Spock is Worried, undated; enlarged and mounted reproduction of full-page magazine ad (Oversize 3)
    - Dr. Benjamin Spock Lecture, undated; Seattle (Oversize 3)
    - Dr. Spock speaks!, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Embrace Peace: Preventing the Last Epidemic / Prescriptions for Survival, undated; sponsored by Physicians for Social Reponsbility (Oversize 3)
    - Emphasis Benjamin Spock, University of Alabama, 1971 (Oversize 3)
    - Grupo UNESCO de Psicoballet Cuba, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Hunterdon Conference on American Problems announces Dr. Benjamin Spock and Leon Bibb, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Lectures and Concerts Committee Presents Dr. Spock, undated (Oversize 3)
    - Massachusetts Civil Liberties Union Foundation Bill of Rights Dinner, 1993 (Oversize 3)
    - Nosotros, La Revolucion, 1970; signed and inscribed to Spock by noted Cuban artist Raul Martinez (Oversize 3)
    - Peace and Freedom Party, 1980; signed by Maureen Walsh (presidential candidate), Elizabeth Barron (VP candidate), and David Wald (U.S. Senator candidate) (Oversize 3)
    - Spock: The Next Generation, [1992]; Pocket Books publicity poster for Baby and Child Care (Oversize 3)
    - Spock Talk, undated; sponsored by Kentucky Civil Liberties Union (Oversize 3)
    - SUB presents Dr. Benjamin Spock Spokesman for the People's Party (Oversize 3)
    - Take Back the Night Rally, Little Rock, undated (Oversize 3)
    - The Wrath of Grapes: Join the Boycott...Again, 1992; signed and inscribed by Cesar Chavez to Mary and Ben (Oversize 3)
    - Yale Political Union Liberal Party presents A Conversation with Dr. Benjamin Spock, "The Future of Democracy in America", undated (Oversize 3)
    - Yale Political Union presents Dr. Benjamin Spock speaking on aspects of Vietnam, undated (Oversize 3)
  - Repair log, Carapace, 1981 (Box 534)
  - Sailing logs, entries often include names of guests, on-shore activities, personal notes, etc.
    - Logs, 1957-1958; 1972-1973,; 1977,; 1979,; 1981-1983; 5 folders (Box 534)
    - Logs, 1984-1986; 4 folders (Box 535)
    - Logs, 1987-1989; 5 folders (Box 536)
    - Logs, 1990-1992; 3 folders (Box 537)
  - School records, 1918-1919; 1921,; 1925; Hamden Hall, Phillips Academy, Yale
  - Scrapbook, "United States Special Delegation to the Inauguration of His Excellency Dr. Arturo Illia, President of the Republic of Argentina", Spock's personal copy, produced by photos, clippings, etc. (Oversize 9)
    See also Argentine Inaugural Ceremonies: United States Delegation.
  - Stamp album (Box 537)
  - To-do lists and telephone notes, 3 folders (Box 538)
  - Wright family, material relating to Mary Morgan's family, including mother Virginia and father Ralph; includes photographs, report cards, schoolbook, drawing, notes for a "Wright family get-together" in 1987, etc.; 2 folders (Box 538)
  - Yearbook, Phillips Academy, 1921 (Box 539)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Argentine Inaugural Ceremonies binder (Box 540)
      See also Argentine Inaugural Ceremonies: United States Delegation; Scrapbook, "United States Special Delegation to the Inauguration of His Excellency Dr. Arturo Illia, President of the Republic of Argentina".
    - Arkansas Democrat-Gazette, "Nixon resigns", 9 Aug 1974; full issue (Oversize 3)
    - Arkansas Democrat-Gazette, Spock article layout, 1 Jan 1995; layout for front page with headline article on Spock, including color separation sheets (Oversize 3)
    - Balloons, "Dr. Spock babies are peace babies", 1 pink, 1 blue; crumbled into dust, discarded; 2 items
    - Bear with axe plaque, metal bear with axe, affixed to wooden plaque; resembles flag from Yaroslavl Region of Russia, appears to have Russian writing on reverse (Box 540)
    - "Dictionary Ben used as a child", circa 1910; Webster's pocket edition (Box 554)
    - License plates, 2 real, from California; one novelty, from Minnesota; 3 items (Box 540)
    - "Mary and Ben" wooden box with needlepoint top (Box 540)
    - Metal molds for signature stamps, Ben's and Mary's (Box 540)
    - New York Post front page, "Arrest Spock" headline, 5 Dec 1967; small mounted reproduction of front page (Oversize 3)
    - Rubber stamp, "Healthy children prefer Spock to Teller", Edward Teller (1908-2003), theoretical physicist known colloquially as "the father of the hydrogen bomb" (Box 540)
    - "Textbook Ben used as a child", 1919; works of Chaucer, Oxford/Clarendon Press (Box 554)
    - Miscellaneous, T-shirt design, business cards, homemade necklace[?], postcard, small card "Practice Nonviolence," Ginger's kindergarten certificate, wristband with Mary Morgan's name, few examples of fan/hate mail, etc.; 3 folders (Box 539)
- Recordings
  - Aboard Carapace (to Ginger and Marb from Ben and MM), Feb 1-8, 1990; spock_b_313; running time 02:00:00; Video-8 (Box 544)
  - Aboard Carapace, Tartola and Peter Islands, Feb-Mar 1990; spock_b_314; running time 02:00:00; Video-8 (Box 544)
  - Against Reason: A Portrait of Jack McClelland, spock_b_300; running time 00:49:20; VHS (Box 543)
  - The Aging Society, Part 13: Growing Old, spock_b_368; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 1 and 2: Introduction and The Childless Society, spock_b_362; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 3 and 4: A New Look at Retirement and Stay Healthy, spock_b_363; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 5 and 6: Are the Young Being Robbed and Women, spock_b_364; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 7 and 8: The Economy and Lifelong Learner, spock_b_365; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 9 and 10: Ethics and Future of the Family, spock_b_366; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - The Aging Society, Part 11 and 12: Power of the Older Voter and Minorities, spock_b_367; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - AIDS-Wise, No Lies (Preview Copy) (P-298), 1988; spock_b_280; running time 00:22:30; VHS (Box 543)
  - AIDS-Wise, No Lies (Preview Copy) (P-321), 1988; spock_b_281; running time 00:22:30; VHS (Box 543)
  - AIM Meeting, New Britain, Conn., Oct. 19, 1966; spock_b_332; Side 1: Rev. Arthur Comeau (w/ guitar) plays and sings peace songs of his own composition. Intro. of candidate - Dr. Edw. Bershtein, U of HTFD. Steve Minot - "A Fresh Approach to Peace in Vietnam." Remarks by Dr. Bershtein - Intro: Dr. Paullin, Central Conn. St. College. Dr. Spock: "For your Children: A World of Peace or a World of War?" (At End - reads letter from W. O. Joseph Samson from Vn.); 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 548)
  - "All Together Now" Dresden, DDR, spock_b_290; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - "All Together Now" Michael Elley and Allen Rosenthall, spock_b_357; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - "Ask Dr Spock", spock_b_295; 2 minute; 1 minute; running time 00:03:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - "Ask Dr. Spock About Baby Care" (Master), 5/7/92; spock_b_293; running time 00:58:16; VHS (Box 543)
  - "Ask Dr. Spock About Child Care" (Master), 5/7/92; spock_b_292; running time 00:52:18; VHS (Box 543)
  - "Ask Dr Spock" TV Ad Excerpts Section No. 2, No. 3, No. 10, spock_b_296; running time 00:30:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Association for International Co-Operation and DIsamament (N.S.W.) - Public Tribute meeting. Sydney Town Hall, Sunday 18th August [no year], spock_b_334; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 550)
  - Association of American Colleges. Two :57 Radio Spots, spock_b_371; Association of American Colleges. Get a liberal education. It's the course for life; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - Association of American Colleges. Two spots, spock_b_372; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - Barnwell Project, 30 Apr 1978; spock_b_127; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Ben 90th Birthday Cleveland, 2 May 1993; spock_b_273; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Ben on Call-in program, Sept. 21, 1984; spock_b_341; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - Ben and Leonard 20 year anniversary party at Mr. Fish, Tortola [Part I], December 12, 1987; spock_b_309; running time 00:30:00; Video-8 (Box 544)
  - Ben and Leonard 20 year anniversary party at Mr. Fish, Tortola [Part II], December 12, 1987; spock_b_310; running time 00:90:00; Video-8 (Box 544)
  - Ben Interview CBS This Morning, 10/1/92; spock_b_242; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 542)
  - Ben Reciting Lord's Prayer, spock_b_143; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Ben Spock 80th birthday party tape, 1983; spock_b_133; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Ben Spock 89 Birthday, May 14, 1992; spock_b_138; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Ben Spock 90th Birthday, 5/2/93; spock_b_272; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Ben Spock: Baby Doctor, spock_b_351; VHS (Box 544)
  - Ben Tributes, spock_b_144; Ben's 95th, Sides 1 and 2; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Ben's Birthday [85th] Party Fort Burt, Tortola, 4/30/88; spock_b_299; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Ben's Interview 20/20 News (ABC), 12/30/94; spock_b_240; running time 00:59:58; VHS (Box 542)
  - Ben's Interview - Dauphin County Library, spock_b_131; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - The Best of Times #40 Ben Spock interview - WAMC Public Radio, spock_b_145; running time 25:09; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Bicentennial Minutes Group 1 and 2, 1/20/76; spock_b_236; running time 00:30:00; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 542)
  - Born Famous Show No. 001 (W.O. No. 24737), 11/02/1987; spock_b_282; running time 00:60:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - "Child Care" #433 Viewpoint, 9/3/1966; spock_b_321; running time 15; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 548)
  - Childhood: Great Expectations: No. 101 (PBS Master Version), 10/14/1991; spock_b_258; running time 00:57:48; VHS (Box 542)
  - Children, Parents & Education, spock_b_118; #3182 1 1/2 hours; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Children, Parents & Education / Benjamin Spock & Claude Steiner / #3182 1 1/2 Hours, spock_b_152; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - Children's Hospital (VanDine Horton MacNamara and Mangus), 12/21/1984; spock_b_266; running time 00:01:00; VHS (Box 542)
  - The Children's Journal. Dr. Rothenberg - TV and Children, 5/3/86; spock_b_339; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - The Children's Journal: Kids in the ‘80s - Dr. Spock, 12/6/86; spock_b_123; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - The Children's Journal - Spock/Councille - Stepfamilies, 3/21/87; spock_b_134; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 547)
  - Contact, WGY Radio with Bob Cudmore Dr. Benjamin Spock; Judith Viorst, 4/30/87; spock_b_347; Side A: Dr. Benjamin Spock; Side B: Judith Viorst; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - "Cosmic Mind" by Irene Margolis, Dennis Perman, and Mitch Clarvit, spock_b_358; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - "Courage Mountain", spock_b_305; VHS (Box 544)
  - Dancing Hands: Visual Arts of Rita Blitt, spock_b_306; running time 00:25:00; VHS (Box 544)
  - Dare to be different: Part 1, spock_b_146; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - Dare to be Different: Part 2, spock_b_147; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - Dixieland Festival, 18th Annual, Dresden, DDR, May 1988; spock_b_289; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Dr Spock - Cambridge Forum West, 7-30-85; spock_b_369; telephone interview from Cambridge Forum West; accompanying letter documents radio show; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 550)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock Today, 9-16-94; spock_b_244; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock March of Time?, spock_b_238; running time 00:30:00; possibly same as spock_b_260; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock: "Parenting in the Nuclear Age" (Berkeley, CA, May 11, 1985; spock_b_261; running time 00:28:56; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock Pittsburgh March of Time, 1955; spock_b_260; possibly same as spock_b_238; running time 00:30:00; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock Profile Barcelona Olympics, 1992; spock_b_253; running time 00:03:12; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock Profile Barcelona Olympics, 1992; spock_b_254; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Benjamin Spock: "Stress Affecting Families and Children" William Rainey Harper College (Lecture Only), 22 Oct 1985; spock_b_298; running time 01:18:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Dr. Spock, 1995; spock_b_256; running time 00:06:23; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Spock Birthday, spock_b_274; running time 02:00:00; VHS (Box 543)
  - Dr. Spock Co. Sales Tape, 9 Apr 2001; spock_b_353; running time 3:15; Betacam Digital (Digi Beta) (Box 544)
  - Dr. Spock Interview (Licensing Services Intl.), 2/1/95; spock_b_255; running time 00:00:24; VHS (Box 542)
  - Dr. Spock "Peace Work" Berkeley Community Theatre, 27 Sep 1968; spock_b_344; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 549)
  - The Dr. Spock Show: Bathing Babies (NBC), 26 Jan 1956; spock_b_315; Film: 16mm
  - The Dr. Spock Show: Toilet Training (No. 1230) (NBC), 9 May 1956; spock_b_316; Film: 16mm
  - Dr. Spock: Time Marches On (30 min), spock_b_239; running time 00:30:00; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 542)